{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","address":"14060 Telegraph Rd","zipcode":"48239","owner":"Dodson R. Batey","licenseNumber":"202812","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/28/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Low","reviewFrequencyDays":"530.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000CC7A899597D154C068D8C72E84314540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41510","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","inspectionDate":"2018-02-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41510","inspectionDate":"2/16/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"41510","inspectionDate":"2/16/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"41510","inspectionDate":"2/16/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Drip Tray","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"41510","inspectionDate":"2/16/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"CLUB","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"36108","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","inspectionDate":"2016-08-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"127","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36108","inspectionDate":"8/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"2-102.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall demonstrate this knowledge by compliance with this Code, by being a certified FOOD protection manager who has shown proficiency of required information through passing a test that is part of an ACCREDITED PROGRAM, or by responding correctly to the inspector's questions as they relate to the specific FOOD operation. (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Does not demonstrate required knowledge","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Knowledge is to be obtained through an approved training program."},{"inspectionid":"36108","inspectionDate":"8/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"outsides of equipment","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"36108","inspectionDate":"8/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."},{"inspectionid":"36108","inspectionDate":"8/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36108","inspectionDate":"8/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"Not provided At hand sink","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"36108","inspectionDate":"8/10/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4368","name":"Club Yesterdays","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4368"}}